CJ WILLIAMS MARKETING & DESIGN PROFESSIONAL



Phone 406.579.1985



Email cj@silencekillsdesign.com



Website

hirecj.netlify.com

SOCIAL



Twitter

@s1lencek1lls



Facebook

/cjwilliamsissilence

in

LinkedIn

/cjwilliamsworks

EDUCATION

Treehouse Academy

Web Development teamtreehouse.com 2014 - 2018

Montana State University

Graphic Design & Music Technology Bozeman, MT 2003 - 2005

SKILLS

- ADOBE CREATIVE CLOUD
- VUE.JS / NUXT / VUEX
- UX / UI DESIGN
- HTML / CSS / JS
- MICROSOFT OFFICE
- SEO / SEM / PPC
- WORDPRESS / WOOCOMMERCE

CERTIFICATIONS

- BEGINNERS GOOGLE ANALYTICS
- ADVANCED GOOGLE ANALYTICS
- HUBSPOT INBOUND MARKETING
- MOZ SEO TRAINING

PROFILE

Hi, I'm CJ! I am an experienced marketing specialist, designer, and front-end developer from Bozeman, MT. I have managed marketing, web development, email campaigns, branding, and design for several companies, delivering quality results. I'm fluent in Adobe Creative Suite, SEO, and front-end development languages and frameworks. I have excellent communication skills, creative talent, marketing sense, and the ability to learn quickly.

EXPERIENCE

Bella Group

Brand Designer / January 2020 - September 2020

- · Brand creation, launch, implementation, and management
- · UX/UI Design and front-end development
- · Motion graphics and presentation design
- · Social media campaign management
- · Email campaign management

SilenceKillsDesign

Owner / 2007 - Present

- · Coordinate with client marketing teams to achieve brand goals
- Modern UX/UI design and development for web applications and user portals
- · Create graphics for digital and print media
- Front-end development, design, and execution
- · Define and implement SEO / SEM strategy
- Track and report on traffic and goal completion in Google Analytics
- · Audio / Video editing for commercials and Internet

Bozeman Curling Club

Marketing Director / 2018 - Present

- Define brand standards and implement with structured naming conventions
- Create graphics for all digital and print media
- · Email campaign management and tracking
- · Sponsorship package creation and sponsor coordination
- · Event planning and coordination with other businesses and non-profits
- · Merchandise sales, screen-printing and promotional orders

Xtant Medical (formerly Bacterin International)

Graphic Design / Marketing Specialist / 2012 - 2016

- · Define brand standards and provide department training for proper usage
- Create graphics for all digital and print media and coordinate with printers
- Web Development for public facing site and internal sales portal
- · Cross-media, location-based campaign planning around tradeshows and events
- · B2B and Internal Email campaign management and tracking
- · Adherence to ISO 13485:2003 quality standards and internal SOP